selectedbrokers.com 2018-12-15

# privacy

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy. \- Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.  
\- We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.  
\- We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.  
\- We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.  
\- Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.  
\- We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.  
\- We use cookies to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners.  
\- We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.  
\- If you have joined our newsletter in the past, you are always able to remove yourself from the list by using the link at the bottom of the newsletter email.  
-Updated April 2018 - the website doesn't currently collect any personal identifiable data nor any other data except the use of services like Google Analytics and Google AdWords.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. You can contact us with any question info@selectedbrokers.com
